http://www.tapesforindustry.co.uk/content/11-privacy-policy

T: 0151 549 2210 E: shop@shandhigson.co.uk Product TypeIndustry TypeBrand
Tesa Adhesives
Home >> Privacy PolicyPrivacy & Data Security Policy Overview…At the Shand Higson group of Companies, (Shand Higson Holdings Ltd, Shand Higson & Co. Ltd & SHC Repack Ltd),  we take you and your data’s security seriously. This policy explains our information practices and policies. It covers how we collect, share and use any personal information we hold. It also explains the choices available to you regarding our use of this information and how you can access and update it.This policy does not reflect the privacy policies or practices of our clients or any other third party. Neither are we responsible for their privacy policies or practices.ScopeThis policy applies to the information we collect when you use one or more of our services, or when you otherwise engage with us, including, but not limited to:when you visit our websitewhen you contact uswhen we connect with you as a prospective client or as a clientwhen you order online through our website shopwhen you meet us at third party events, gatherings or meetups.Information collection and processingWe primarily collect personal information that is necessary for us to provide our services to clients. We will also collect personal information in the ordinary course of running our business, including through the receipt of communications such as emails, website enquiries and telephone calls.When we refer to “personal information”, we mean individually identifiable information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate a specific person.  This information may include:First name, last name, email address, job title, phone numbers.Preferences information such as notification and marketing preferences.Company and billing information such as billing address, headquarters address and place of work.We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymised.By providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of our services.Other dataWe may collect personal data that you submit to us via our website or third-party tools including, for example, when applying for a job via our website or requesting support in relation to one of our services.Analytics and logsWe collect analytics and log information when you use our website to improve our products and services.IP Addresses and cookiesA cookie, also known as an HTTP cookie, web cookie, or browser cookie, is usually a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while a user is browsing a website. When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user’s previous activity. Cookies are not viruses, spyware, or trojans that cause harm to your machine.Our website uses a variety of cookies to help improve the quality of your experience:Essential & Functional Cookies Without these cookies certain functions of our website would not work, such as login, registration and password areas.Analytics Cookies These cookies monitor how visitors use our website. This helps us to improve the customer flow and provide additional resources for popular pages.Third Party Cookies These are cookies dropped onto your device by other websites, for example, if we host a video on YouTube.com and embed that on our site, when you click play YouTube drops a cookie onto your device, so it knows you have watched it. We do try, wherever possible, to only allow third-party cookies to be dropped onto your device from websites we trust.Session Cookies If you have arrived at any of our websites by clicking on a banner advertisement for one of products or services, a session cookie may be used. This cookie contains an identification number for the advertisement that you clicked on, and it helps us determine which of our adverts attracts the most visitors.Persistent Cookies In order to better understand how our sites are used, we may also use persistent cookies along with other information collected in our servers' files (e.g., IP Address, referring URLs, etc.). Such information is not combined with information from any other cookie. Cookies may be delivered in a first-party or third-party context.Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical / performance cookies or targeting cookies.Device related informationWe may also collect device related information from a user’s device(s), including information such as an IP address, operating system, the date and time of use of our services, system logs, and technical attributes about the device or a web browser.Where we store your personal informationAll information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers within the EU. We take all appropriate measures to ensure data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy. We have adopted physical, technological, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the data we process. We enforce least privilege access policies for our employees on all data. Our Systems Controller is responsible for maintenance and operation of all information technology risk management programs, security controls and activities.RetentionWe retain your personal information needed to provide our services only so long as we have a valid business purpose, in accordance with applicable law and our client agreements. We may retain aggregated and anonymised information indefinitely.We do not store credit or debit card details.Information SharingWe will not sell or rent your personal information, nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. However, we may share or disclose your personal information as follows:We may provide your information to our business partners, vendors or service providers who perform functions on our behalf in line with our service agreements, for example a parcel delivery service.In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.As required by law, government officials, or other third parties pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process or requirement applicable to our company.When we believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss.To report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of our agreements.Children’s privacyOur services are not directed towards minors. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided information to us through our websites or services, please contact us and we will delete that information from our databases.Accessing and updating your informationIf you wish to request access to, correction, or deletion of personal information you have submitted through our website, you can contact us at legal@shandhigson.co.uk. We will respond to your request within 30 days.ChangesWe may amend this policy from time to time. When there are changes we will update this page.Contact usIf you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact Mark Dyos by emailing legal@shandhigson.co.uk.Shand Higson Holdings LtdLees Road Knowsley Industrial Park North Knowsley Merseyside L33 7SEEffective DateThis Privacy & Data Protection Policy became effective on 25th May 2018.
